dvdtalk.com 2007-06-17

# Privacy Statement for DVD Talk/ Kleinman.com Inc.

| **DVD & MOVIE REVIEWS**  
---  

**DVD TALK FORUM**  
**Forum Area:**  
**REVIEWS & COLUMNS**  
• [DVD Reviews](http://www.dvdtalk.com/reviews/index.php)  
• [Theatrical Reviews](http://www.dvdtalk.com/reviews/list.php?reviewType=Theatrical)  
• [Video Game Reviews](http://www.dvdtalk.com/reviews/games/list.php)  
• [Adult DVD Reviews](http://www.dvdtalk.com/reviews/list.php?reviewType=Adult+DVD+Video)  
• [DVD Interviews](http://www.dvdtalk.com/dvdinterviews.html)

• [The Aisle View](http://www.aisleview.com/index.html)  
• [The Blue Room](http://www.dvdtalk.com/adult/index.html)  
• [Cinema Gotham](http://www.dvdtalk.com/cinemagotham/index.html)  
• [CineSchlock-O-Rama](http://www.dvdtalk.com/cineschlock/index.html)  
• [DVD Savant](http://www.dvdtalk.com/dvdsavant/index.html)  
  
**SHOP**  
• [Adult DVD Empire](http://www.adultdvdempire.com/index.asp?partner_id=59826076)  
• [Amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect-home/dvdtalk) ([DVD](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=dvdtalk&path=subst/video/dvd/dvd.html))  
• [Buy.com](http://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=cZdGXyuEAtc&offerid=37803.10000207&type=3&subid=0)  
• [DeepDiscountCD](http://www.deepdiscountcd.com/index.cfm?goto=home&referral=dvdtalk)  
• [DeepDiscountDVD](http://www.deepdiscountdvd.com/redirect.cfm?referral=dvdtalkedt&goto=home)  
• [DVD Empire](http://www.dvdempire.com/index.asp?partner_id=49648684)  
• [DVD Overnight](http://www.dvdovernight.com/index.asp?affil_id=PF2U4JP0)  
• [DVD Planet](http://service.bfast.com/bfast/click?bfmid=26864318&siteid=30217318&bfpage=home)  
• [Ebay](http://www.qksrv.net/click-280928-1643272)  
• [Half.com](http://www.qksrv.net/click-280928-167876)  
• [HKFlix.com](http://www.hkflix.com/xq/asp/aid.007782/qx/home.htm)  
• [HTMarket.com](http://www.htmarket.com/)  
• **[Complete List of Stores](http://www.dvdtalk.com/support.html)**  
**DVD RESOURCE**  
• [DVD Talk Forum](http://www.dvdtalk.com/forum/index.php)  
• [DVD Price Search](http://www.dvdtalk.com/price.html)  
• [Store Ratings](http://www.dvdtalk.com/store.html)  
• [Customer Service #'s](http://www.dvdtalk.com/csr.html)  
• [DVD FAQ](http://www.dvdtalk.com/faq.html)  
• [Regional Encoding Info](http://www.dvdtalk.com/rce.html)  
• [Search Toolbar](http://www.dvdtalk.com/dvdtalkinanutshell.html)  
• [Links](http://www.dvdtalk.com/links.html)  
**DVDTALK INFO**  
• [About DVD Talk](http://www.dvdtalk.com/welcome.html)  
• [Advertise](http://www.dvdtalk.com/ad.html)  
• [Contribute](http://www.dvdtalk.com/contribute.html)  
• [Tell A Friend](http://www.dvdtalk.com/recommend.html)  
• [Newsletter Subscribe](http://www.dvdtalk.com/subscribe.html)  
• [Join DVD Talk Forum](http://www.dvdtalk.com/forum/register.php) [](http://bilbo.counted.com/7/23448/)  

**Privacy Statement for DVD Talk/ Kleinman.com Inc.**

Privacy Statement for DVD Talk/ Kleinman.com Inc.

## Privacy Statement for DVD Talk

Kleinman.com Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: DVD Talk.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

This site contains links to other sites. **DVD Talk** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers (like social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Choice/Opt-Out

We useand other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

## Third Party Advertising

We use Google Adwords, Tribal Fusion and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please[Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

## Third Party Cookies 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, any of our third-party ad server: Google Ads, Tribal Fusion, Atlas or their affiliates, or individual advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. * Note our Ad server is Adcycle, it's not a third party service or system it is our internal ad server. 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

## DVD Talk Nutshell Toolbar

The DVD Talk Nutshell Toolbar is designed for utility and as such does not require you to disclose your personal information to download and use it. The Toolbar does not monitor or individually track your usage, is in no way Spyware and should not interfere in any way with your searches (ie no pop-ups, unders, co-opted links, etc). The only tracking information used by the DVD Talk Nutshell Toolbar are the affiliate links at several of the listed retailers. This is designed to give DVD Talk credit for sales generated by the Toolbar and not for any other purpose. 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [talk@dvdtalk.com](mailto:talk@dvdtalk.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Geoffrey Kleinman Kleinman.com Inc. 8872 SW 82nd Ave Portland, OR 97223 talk@dvdtalk.com

Columns

|
